It's 5:00 in the evening and I'm on my way to
Dehradun to meet the man whose
car worth ₹33 lakh just fell into a ditch.
Oh hello hello sir how are you?  Oh, what a
wonderful surprise.  Move this camera a little to the
side.  We're just going to shoot.
Bhai himself is a creator and is the
most hyped person at the moment.  Not for any good thing, but for something
which they will probably
never be able to say in their life.  A smiling
face does not mean that he is not in any pain.
[Song voice]
Brother, he still bought Mahindra's XUV 9 by
spending ₹33 lakh and because of someone else's mistake,
brother, the car fell into a deep ditch hundreds of kilometers below.
When the car fell into the ditch, the brother himself was
driving the car.  The car is completely destroyed
but brother is standing alive without any scratch.
Brother, tell me one thing,
how did you survive?  [MUSIC]
All the air bags deployed.  Safety is no doubt
excellent.  The safety is very good.   The
entire car was damaged.  All its air
bags had opened.  And look at the condition
of the car.  [Music] What a state it had become.
Despite that, I and one of my friends were also with us.  There were
minor scratches
that occur on glass.  Nothing else except that.
Tell me when did you buy the car and
how did the accident happen?  Tell me a little bit about that.
My car was delivered on 7th August.
After that I
drove it a little bit.  Then I shot a video in
which I explained the tech features etc.
After that we just gave it for PPF etc.
I personally ran 100 km.   Had
driven it.  Totally this is 500 km.  She had left.
The night I received the delivery from PPF.
[groaning sound]
Now when we left, we went to eat something
ahead like, come on, my friend is here, let's eat something together.  Were coming back.  There
is a very sharp turn there and I was coming from there.
A car came from the front and it
was on almost the wrong side and that wrong side is such that
if I show you now what is the
condition of that road ahead.  There 90% of the
vehicles come on the wrong side.  Because
his size is nothing.  He steered
a little left and there were no barricades there
and went straight ahead.  When its impact
came, there is
a video of that impact too,
I will share it with you.  All the air bags inside it had
opened.  Smoke comes out as the air bags open inside.
So when smoke came in it,
I was completely shaken from within.  I
think brother, something is going to happen.
Get out quickly.  I got a call in the car.  SOS received a
call from the emergency people saying that your
SOS call has been received here.  You have had an accident.
I said yes the car overturned.  This
door was jammed.
My friend and I
came out from the driver's side from where the impact occurred.  But one thing is that
when brother uploaded this story,
brother, what can I say, some
brainless people were commenting on Twitter that this is
why we do not buy any car of Indian brand.   I
mean, how is this possible? I did not understand
what kind of mentality these people have that they have
a big example in front of them that
this person is alive because of an Indian brand car.
Today he is
able to post the video in front of us.  Because of one Indian
brand car, there are
so many brands in India today.  They have started paying attention to safety so that despite so much happening, nothing happened to
you.  Because of Indian brand
cars, today we can see ads
in such an affordable range in cars worth ₹10-15 lakh to ₹20 lakh
because
Mahindra was the first to give this in 7W itself.  Tata pays a
lot of attention to safety.   I
mean, at least these are the people who, while
living in India, are
enemies of India.  He made a hole in the plate in which he ate.  I
mean friend, at least if you cannot support then at
least do not spread such negative things.
Half the people watch the video half-heartedly
or do not understand it completely.  The
three biggest blames I have put on him.
First of all, we will show the government what we have
in that area.  Secondly, ICICI
Lombard, which is my insurance company, did
not provide any support.  Third
Mahindra after sales service.
Not a Mahindra car.  I directly appreciated the Mahindra car saying
that brother, I was
saved because of it.  No doubt safety is great.
And yes, let me tell you again that there is no problem with the car.
Safety wise
is great.
Brother, tell me once what was the reaction of Mahindra people after
seeing this car?
This was my reaction on seeing the car, Bhaiya, first of all they were
saying that Bhaiya you are absolutely fine, there is no
injury, no bone fracture, I
mean nobody was so sure that they were
not believing that the guy is
standing alive, I and my friend were also there, so
both of us went and then when
next day I told them Bhaiya
how will it be done, they were saying Bhaiya we will
make the quotation right now, they took
almost a week to make the quotation, whatever inspection they were
doing, I am talking about the guy from Mahindra,
first he gave a quotation of ₹56 lakh to
ICICI LBA people, for
₹6 lakh, for
₹56 lakh. Now everyone must be thinking
that when the car costs ₹33 lakh, then
how did the cost come to ₹56 lakh, so when you go to calculate the price of each part like this, then
it becomes expensive like this.  If you
look at this watch, it might have come for ₹1,000 to ₹15,000.
But when I go to take out its lace and the
needles inside it,
it becomes expensive.  So in this
way ₹56 lakh means total lost car.
Yes, totally lost.  What did he do?
They also included the battery.   The
motor inside it, the main motor, is worth ₹10
lakhs, so the two components are the same.
Apart from that, they added the entire car, seats, videos,
everything, infotainment.  Then the
surveyor from the insurance company came and
inspected the car again.
They cut everything cross cross cross like this
that this is also fine, this is also fine, this is also fine,
this is also fine and yes it is
₹11 lakh plus GST, earned his quotation of 13-14 lakh
in hand,
from the quotation of ₹1 lakh directly ICICI
shifted it to ₹11 lakh that the car will be completely repaired in ₹11 lakh,
and start the repair in ₹1 lakh,
I have got the mail also, start it
and this was made by those people who do not even know
how Mahindra cars are repaired.
Then how can Mahindra or any
brand's vehicles be correct? The most
interesting thing is that the
model written on the quotation was XUV 700.  XUV 9
was also not written.
Really
yes sir.
Meaning the name of this car should have been mentioned here.
He has written 7O there.
He has mentioned it there.  Meaning they don't even
know which car this is?
Absolutely.   He
made a quotation of ₹11 lakh and gave it.   It was a
simple matter that Mahindra people gave it for ₹56
lakh.  Companies
want to save their costs in this way.  So he gave ₹11 lakh.
That is their job.  That is his job.  But did
Mahindra people
not argue here at all that
this car could not be repaired without ₹56 lakh or ₹50 lakh.
This car will not be repaired for ₹11 lakh.
I made multiple visits to Mahindra
workshop and asked them why are you not giving them counter quotation
?  You should get the
car inspected again.  He is saying that
sir, this is the only expense.  And after that, how much
time did they take to repair this car
?
Yes, I also had a major concern in that as to
how many days you will take.  He said
you will get the car in a month or less.  There
is no such tension.  It will be done quickly
because all the parts are changed in it.
Nothing gets repaired.  After that
he spent three months.  That means when I signed the
agreement, I signed it on 17th October.
November December I got the car on January 29th.  That
means you spent about one and a half
months fighting that fight
and after that you got this car after about six months.   It's been a
total of 4 months.
4 month.
Okay brother, now after buying this car
you are driving it.  What shortcomings do you feel right
now?  It looks like this.  I have bought this second
hand car.  After spending so much money.
While the AC is on silent [music].
Any car as of today.  And the
cabin of an EV is very silent anyway.   It is
very silent.
Now after some time, some strange
humming sound will come in it.   Look,
she has come.   I am
also feeling scared.
Something like this wheel is moving inside.
Yes yes yes.  So some fittings have not been done properly by
them.
Everything is the fault of ICICI people.  But
still Mahindra's work has been done here.
That's the point, isn't it?  Ultimately
he made us agree that we will make it.
Yes.   Do
n't agree to this.  The work should have been done well and
at least the customer should have been told that the car belongs to
him.  Now that I have experienced this car, let me
tell you what all the
Mahindra dealership has done to this car in 4 1/2 months.  At
first,
you won't be able to tell much in the sunlight, its
paint quality is absolutely zero.  After that,
when this car met with an accident, this
rubber got cut here.  This rubber is still
cut even today.  And after that,
look at the hinges here, brother, I will
paint it better than this at home.  This is such a bad paint.  The
paint is so poor.  And then there's one
more thing.
You see,
this part here, I just saw that
you cannot adjust the height of this seat belt.
I pressed this button and it remained
pressed down below.  It hasn't happened up there.  It is
not happening here either.   That's
why brother, I am telling you genuinely that after
driving this car, it does not feel at all that
I am driving a new car.   It
feels like my Thar is one and a half years old.  Brother, he has
better finishing today.  She
shines more.  The thing is that it was kept
parked somewhere in the junk for five-
six months and the swell marks that appear there are there at
many places on the car.   There are
so many marks, Sk was making noise again.
Yes, it will keep making this noise again.
So now you should make this a habit.  I have put it in.
[laughter] Let me
tell you one more thing.  When
they prepared this car, the three-
point seat belt did
not have the point to attach the third seat belt.
I covered that in the video as well.
You have that covered as well.  And
what about the guy who came to fix it?   On
top of that he is saying that brother, it will not come out
because there is a lock in it and this one
also.  If both of them leave, his seat will have to be
cancelled.  [laughter]
Hey brother, I said you are saying that the company fitted car will have to be
cut.  Well,
its sensors are working very well.
I just tried adaptive cruise control on it and
it is working well.
Lane assist, which includes automatic
steering, etc., and
automatic braking while reversing.  So the sensors are working fine till now,
which gives me some satisfaction
that yes, there is no problem right now.
What scares you the most about this car
?
Of the air bag?  [laughter]
Once they opened up.   The very
thing that saved me, I will never take it.
God forbid this happens again.
Then they will open.  Now this thing is such that it
cannot even be tested.
This is the place where your car fell into the ditch.
Yes, I was coming from there.
And this barricade was not there then.
But the rest of us were these ones, but right
now these are also missing.  Meaning,
after your accident,
someone else's car also collided here and he fell
inside.
100% because it is not as deep as it
appears here right now.  This was deeper at that time.
They have filled it up a little more by cutting down the trees.
But no work was done on safety.
Meaning, the government understood only this much
that just to show off to the people,
they have filled the pit a little by throwing garbage here.
Apart from this, no
brother worked on barricading here.
I just saw my brother's video here and
it was not colored here.  Now all
they understood was that they should paint it
and put a red strip on it.
Apart from that, brother, the barge gate has not been installed even today.  It
means that if someone dies, let him die, but collecting tax
means how to collect maximum tax.
But brother, there is
no work on safety.  Go to the local one and
see.   Yes yes
absolutely.  Look, this
also collided just now.  Yes, this was correct earlier.
Look, there are glasses lying here too.
Oh
brother, there are glasses lying here.   There has been a
recent accident.
Hello brother.
You live right here.   There
is no barricading etc. here.   Do
accidents keep happening here?
Yes, they keep happening.   There were
many cars after that.
But the accident was not major.  Consider it a blessing
that no major accident happened to anyone.
You help etc. when something happens here, you should do it,
ask them, all the
locals had gathered in front, around 11:30 pm,
you were helping them here till 11:30 pm,
but it seems like the government here does not do any work, would it be a
little bit okay, according to the liquor, they would
make a mess, then after driving away, some would
lose their car, I
mean such things keep happening
in the mountains, accidents etc.,
when there are vehicles, big
things happen, but the thing is that there is
no work on safety, when an
accident happens, it is known that a
vehicle has collided here, so much loss has happened, then at
least go and barricade the place, put
reflector tape here, at
least
I am living in Dehradun for 10 years now, I
know
how many turns this road has, there is something, but the
vehicle that came from the front and it happened, I
mean at night we don't know  There is a gap in the light
between the vehicles, that happens
but like today we have come to
ask you that does this keep happening here, is there no
government official, no
municipality, no one here, no one has come to
ask, no one,
first of all you are the one who has come for the first time, that
means you are telling this comfortably and happily
that nothing has happened, that means there was not much impact,
we are the first ones.  No one
raises voice for this.  No one raises their voice, no one.
No one cares.   If
someone close to the government passes away, then perhaps
they will feel that now let's make something.   Okay,
fine.  Thank you brother.  You please help me
whenever anything happens.  Even if the government does
n't help, you should help, friend.  Sure?
Sure.
Promise.
Brother, the people here are very supportive but the
government is not.  Not at all.   The
government does not care at all.
After that, as soon as I saw it, I understood that
these screw marks
appear only when a part is opened using a screwdriver.
And there are thousands of such marks on this car.   The
entire car has been destroyed.
After that when I opened the bonnet, look at this.  All this is
shaking.  These hooks that are here, there are
no hooks on this side.  There
is nothing here.  This is proper tight.
After that, look, even if
I take this out and take it home, it doesn't make any difference.
All this is such a part.  Here, as soon as you
open it upwards, you will see that this
screw is not fitted properly.
I will open this also with my hands.
Yellow.
Now there will be thousands of such things in it.  A
person can see such things from outside.  Who
knows, there might be similar screws fitted below which might
not open today and according to me, while
driving you might cover 100-200 km.
The day you drive it, who knows it might open and fall.
Who knows, you might also fall down.  These were the
shortcomings which I understood as soon as I sat
in your car.  Apart from this, some
noise also comes in your car from here.
When you drive, it makes a sound like 'khat khat khat khat'
because this was the impacted area on the
left.  So, whenever the
road becomes a little uneven or there is a
speed breaker, a rattling
sound is heard from this area.  And even when we turn it on or off, the
car makes an odd sound which
you just noticed.
When I was sitting in the car and
started it, it felt like
[music] it is
starting like this, it doesn't happen in EV vehicles.   There is
no sound of anything in EV vehicles.
He is very silent and says not now.  This is the
kind of sound that means I am
sitting in this car for the first time today and I am
feeling scared, so what must be happening to you.
What might be happening in this?  There are so many
things like its gear console has
marks and
scratches from all over the world.  There is an infotainment system.
Whereas it was not even damaged.   That
gear is not even on the console, sir.
All the glossy parts of your car have become
so dirty at this time as if the
car has been parked outside for five-six months and
anything is entering it.  This is what
happened.  5-6 months ago, when this car met with an
accident, there was a lot of rain in
Dehradun and it was
standing outside in his workshop during the rains.  Apart from these things, are there
any other problems you are facing with this car
?  Yes, as long as the video was there,
I had told a lot of things in it.
Right now its Android Auto glitching.
Sometimes it works and sometimes it doesn't
and there is no lag at all in it.
[Music] Like a call came in and the song
lagged.  Meaning it will freeze completely.   No matter
how much you touch it, it doesn't move.
Now, brother, there are
paint marks on its hydraulic too.  Meaning the
paint is of such poor quality.  If I were there,
I would not have taken the car under any circumstances.
Bhai, how can he do this [music] he took the
car, I mean, even after so much support,
how can someone do this to a person, to a customer?  Tell me one small
thing.  We missed that in this video.
When this car was completed, for which
they had given an estimate of ₹1 lakh or ₹11 lakh, how much did it cost
?
Yes, that is a major thing.  Its quotation had reached around ₹16 lakh ₹15
lakh plus GST ₹1.5 lakh.
And
if we add up all the shortcomings it still has, then it is
completely eligible to go into total loss condition.
Now apart from what I mentioned, there are
other shortcomings inside the car.   There are
many shortcomings, brother, I have written them down.
Hey brother, I have made a list.  What should I do,
how much should I remember someone?  I remembered from the list that
when I uploaded the first video, the next
day five
people came to my house from Mahi's workshop.  Sir, tell me
what shortcomings we have.  So we
wrote down the shortcomings on the paper and gave it to them.  There were 30-33
factors, whatever small
screw-wrap of paint, all this was written down.  Now we forgot to
take his photo.  He took it and went away.
I told him, Sir, please send me that photo.
His message comes, Sir that paper is lost.
Look, he has done the finishing with a paint brush.  And
such accountability brothers with paint brushes are
everywhere.  The front USB port is not working.
Wired charging works.  The USB port,
whether it is wired Car Play or wired
Android Auto or the one that we need to
transfer the footage etc., is
not working in the phone.   There was
also a sensor issue inside it.  Its
headlamps were turning on automatically.  Were going
off.  This happened on the moving highway.   The
light is turning on automatically.  It is getting off
at night.  At night and then one more thing I
saw was the key ECU
in your car.
We have kept its key fob inside, you can
keep it anywhere in the cabin, anywhere in the front or back
and you can get out of the car.   It does
n't even detect keypop.
If you keep it in a particular space where there is a
wireless charger etc.  Apart
from that, if you keep it behind then it detects it.
So there is probably
some issue with the connection of some sensors.  So he does too.
A battery also has a good function inside.  As soon as you
sit in the car, the low voltage
contact comes written Mahindra Support
and the battery sign comes.  Now
I don't know how serious he is or how serious he is not.
Either the wire that was cut below was
not of that or it was of the sensor,
what wire was cut?
Well, not to you, but
under the driver's seat, they had left a completely naked wire
under the driver's seat,
and brother, it is
not at all like they have any enmity with Mahindra.  He
still appreciates Mahindra for
making a very good car.  I can't even talk about them.  Whatever he is
saying after seeing his car, he is telling about the after sales service of the
dealership and the bad experience he had because of ICICI.
Now I feel that
whatever work needs to be done on your vehicle, at
least you are a Mahindra customer, Mahindra should do
so much that at
least proper action should be taken against the dealership.
Exactly what
brother, everything was damaged so much.
Why didn't you take action after the damage occurred?
At least the work done after that has been done here at Mahindra.  So at
least there should have been some finishing in it.
So Mahindra should do this much
that they get their car back once.
All the [music] things should be
checked once again and the
repainted parts of the car which have not been repainted today should be
completely changed and not
repainted again because the
finishing will not be achieved otherwise.  These
parts should be replaced again.  The
glitches should be rectified and those who are
seeing that they have
put these screw marks at various places.  These things
should be resolved again because
Mahindra is a very good company after all and
I think that if the people who were tweeting to you were
even in America then a
company like Tesla would not have been formed today.
Correct.
Okay, right?  So after all, we should
support the Indian companies here.
Because the product is being made very well.
Just do a little work on the after sales service.
Whatever little experience of a person has been
spoiled, connect it back.
So brother, this was in today's video.  If you
liked the video then please like it
and if something similar has happened to you
with any other brand then
please tell us in the comment section.  We will do as much
support as we can and
we will bring your [music] story the same way.
If you also had a bad experience, then
brother, everyone is an important customer for us
[music] brother, no one's
experience should be bad.  See you
in the next video.  Till then
bye
and thank you Anil Bhai for coming.